export const containerTitle = {
    "/": [{ title: "Y2Meta - YouTube Downloader", desc: "Download YouTube videos seamlessly in 1080p with Y2meta" }],
    "/youtube-to-mp3/": [{ title: "YouTube To MP3 Converter", desc: "Convert YouTube video in MP3 format in the highest quality with the y2meta tool." }],
    "/youtube-to-mp4/": [{ title: "YouTube To MP4 Converter", desc: "Convert and download YouTube videos to MP4 format seamlessly in HD up to 4K." }],
}

export const features = [
    {
        imgClass: 'fast',
        title: 'Fast Download',
        description: 'Unlike other YouTube downloader tools that take you through multiple screens to save YouTube videos, Y2Meta allows you to simply paste the video link to download, making the process faster.'
    },
    {
        imgClass: 'multiple',
        title: 'Multiple Video Qualities',
        description: 'When you download a YouTube video from Y2Meta, you have several options. For MP4 downloads, we offer multiple video qualities, such as 360p, 720p, 1080p, 2K, and up to 4K.'
    },
    {
        imgClass: 'unlimited',
        title: 'Unlimited Downloads',
        description: 'With Y2Meta, you can download an unlimited number of YouTube videos by repeating the same process as many times as you want. There are no limitations on downloading videos and audio. Enjoy our unlimited YouTube video downloader tool, Y2Meta.'
    },
    {
        imgClass: 'nologin',
        title: 'No Login Or Signup',
        description: 'We never ask our users to enter any personal details to download YouTube videos. Simply search for our website, enter the URL, and download it. This makes us safer and more secure for YouTube video downloads.'
    }
];

export const homeFaqs = [
    {
        question: "What is Y2Meta?",
        answer: "Y2Meta is an online tool that allows users to download YouTube videos offline in high-quality MP3 and MP4 formats."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I download a complete YouTube playlist with Y2Meta?",
        answer: "Yes, you can. Simply paste the YouTube video link into the search box, and while downloading, choose the playlist download option to proceed. You can also download single videos from a YouTube playlist."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I use Y2Meta on a mobile phone?",
        answer: "Y2Meta works well on all devices, including mobile phones, desktops, tablets, and more. So yes, you can use the Y2Meta YouTube downloader tool seamlessly on your mobile phone."
    },
    {
        question: "Is it safe to use Y2meta?",
        answer: "Yes, we never ask for any of your data, which makes us a safe YouTube downloader tool. Since this is a web-based platform, there is no need to download any mobile app or software. Y2Meta is an SSL-certified and trusted website to use."
    },
    {
        question: "What qualities y2meta provides for MP4 video download?",
        answer: "You can download videos in various qualities, ranging from low to high, such as 360p, 720p, 1080p, 2K, and up to 4K. Additionally, by using Y2Meta, you can download high-quality videos at lightning-fast speeds with small file sizes for quicker downloads."
    },
    {
        question: "Where will my MP4 and MP3 files be saved?",
        answer: "You can find the downloaded files in your file manager or your 'Downloads' folder. If you have any difficulties locating your downloaded files, feel free to contact us, and we will guide you."
    },
    {
        question: "Which browsers does Y2Meta support?",
        answer: "As Y2Meta is built with the latest tech stack, it works smoothly on all browsers, including Chrome, Edge, Safari, Mozilla, Opera, Brave, and more."
    },
    {
        question: "Do I need to pay to use Y2Meta?",
        answer: "No, it is a free tool for downloading YouTube videos, so there is no need to pay. We don't have any subscription plans. To provide you with high-quality YouTube videos, we show you some ads to monetize the service."
    }
];

export const mp3Features = [
    {
        imageClass: "fast",
        title: "Multiple Formats",
        description: "Y2Meta offers a range of audio formats to suit your needs, including MP3, WEBM, MPEG, WAV, FLAC, and more. If you're converting YouTube to audio for the first time and are unsure which format to choose, we recommend downloading in MP3, as it’s compatible with most devices."
    },
    {
        imageClass: "multiple",
        title: "High-Quality Audio",
        description: "Download YouTube audio (MP3) in various bitrates, including 96kbps, 128kbps, 192kbps, 256kbps, and up to the highest quality of 320kbps. Select your preferred high-quality MP3 format and download it for free."
    },
    {
        imageClass: "unlimited",
        title: "No App Required",
        description: "Y2Meta’s YouTube to MP3 converter is a web-based tool that does not require downloading any mobile application or software to convert and download YouTube videos in MP3 format. Simply visit our website to easily save videos as MP3 files."
    },
    {
        imageClass: "nologin",
        title: "No Annoying Ads",
        description: "Unlike other YouTube MP3 converter tools that require signing up and displaying excessive ads before downloading, Y2Meta allows you to browse the website, enter the YouTube video URL, convert it to MP3, and download it directly—without disruptive ads."
    }
];

export const mp3FaqData = [
    {
        question: "What is a YouTube MP3 Converter Tool?",
        answer: "Y2Meta is a YouTube to MP3 converter tool that allows you to save YouTube videos in MP3 format for offline access. Y2Meta simplifies YouTube to MP3 conversion with its fast and easy-to-use online converter tool, which is free to use."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I Save YouTube Videos in MP3 Format Using My iPhone?",
        answer: "Yes, you can access the Y2Meta website on any device, whether it’s an iPhone, Android, Mac, Windows, or any other operating system. All you need is a web browser and a stable internet connection to convert YouTube videos to MP3 for free."
    },
    {
        question: "How to Save MP3 from YouTube?",
        answer: "Follow these simple steps to convert and download YouTube videos in MP3 format:",
        steps: [
            "Search for 'YouTube to MP3 Converter,' and you’ll find the Y2Meta website among the top results.",
            "Open the website, enter the copied YouTube video URL in the search bar, or search for the video title, and click 'Convert.'",
            "Select your preferred MP3 bitrate (quality) and format, then click the 'Download' button to start downloading to your device."
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Is This an Unlimited YouTube MP3 Converter?",
        answer: "Yes, Y2Meta allows you to convert an unlimited number of videos to MP3 format without any restrictions. Simply repeat the conversion process to save multiple videos in MP3 format."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I Search for the Video I’m Looking For?",
        answer: "Yes, Y2Meta is not just a top YouTube to MP3 converter tool; it also functions as a search engine for downloading MP3 songs. You can search for videos as you would on YouTube and get direct download options in both MP3 and MP4 formats."
    }
];

export const mp4Features = [
    {
        iconClass: "fast",
        title: "Multiple Video Qualities",
        description: " Most YouTube MP4 download tools provide only 720p downloads, but y2meta allows you to save YouTube videos in multiple HD qualities, such as 320p, 480p, 720p, 1080p, 2K, and up to 4K on supported devices. You can choose your preferred video quality when you enter the YouTube video URL."
    },
    {
        iconClass: "multiple",
        title: "Fast Conversion Speed",
        description: "Our tool uses the latest technology stack, and the video downloading and converting process is powered by fast cloud technology, making us one of the fastest YouTube MP4 converter tools. Additionally, there's no need for login or registration, saving you time and enhancing security."
    },
    {
        iconClass: "unlimited",
        title: "Easy to Use",
        description: "Y2meta’s YouTube to MP4 Converter tool offers a straightforward MP4 conversion and download process. Simply open our official YT MP4 converter website, paste the YouTube link, select the MP4 quality, and hit the download button to save the video offline for free."
    },
    {
        iconClass: "nologin",
        title: "Cross-Browser Compatibility",
        description: "Our tool is designed to work seamlessly across all major web browsers, including Chrome, Edge, Safari, Mozilla, and many more. Plus, as the website is responsive, it works well on all OS and device types. Try it now!"
    }
];

export const mp4FaqData = [
    {
        question: "What is YouTube to MP4 Converter?",
        answer: "The YouTube to MP4 Converter is an online, web-based tool that allows you to convert and save YouTube videos in MP4 format for offline viewing, with various video quality options, all for free"
    },
    {
        question: "Is it Safe to Convert YouTube to MP4 Using Y2Meta?",
        answer: "Absolutely. Y2Meta is a 100% safe online MP4 converter tool trusted by millions globally, with SSL certification. Moreover, Y2Meta doesn’t ask for personal information such as name, email, or contact details, making it a secure choice for converting videos to MP4 format."
    },
    {
        question: "How to Use the Free YouTube to MP4 Converter Tool?",
        answer: "Using this MP4 converter tool is easy with just two steps:",
        steps: [
            "Go to the official Y2Meta website and paste the YouTube video URL in the search box, or directly search for the video you want.",
            "Select your preferred video quality and format, then hit the download button to save it offline.'",
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Are There Any Limitations to Converting YouTube to MP4?",
        answer: "No, this is an unlimited YouTube MP4 converter tool. There are no restrictions on converting multiple YouTube videos to MP4, and it's completely free!"
    },
    {
        question: "Is Any Software Required to Use Y2Meta?",
        answer: "No, there’s no need to download software or a mobile app. All you need is a stable internet connection, a web browser, and the YouTube video URL you want to save in MP4 format."
    },
    {
        question: "Is Y2Meta Accessible in Multiple Languages?",
        answer: "Yes, the website is available in over 38 languages, including English, Spanish, Portuguese, Filipino, Dutch, and more. You can change the website language from the top navigation bar."
    },
    {
        question: "How to Contact the Y2Meta Team for Support?",
        answer: "If you encounter any issues while converting YouTube videos to MP4, feel free to reach out to us via our contact email or contact form."
    },
];